codero.com 2017-06-23

# Codero Privacy Policy

                                                                                               Codero Privacy Policy
General: Codero Hosting is committed to protecting your privacy. This Privacy Policy will explain to you our policies
for collecting, using, and disclosing personally identifiable information that you provide to us. By submitting your
personally identifiable information to us you agree to the terms of this Privacy Policy.
We comply with the U.S.-EU Safe Harbor Framework and the U.S.-Swiss Safe Harbor Framework as set forth by the
U.S. Department of Commerce regarding the collection, use, and retention of personal information from European
Union member countries and Switzerland. We have certified that we adhere to the Safe Harbor Privacy Principles
of notice, choice, onward transfer, security, data integrity, access, and enforcement. To learn more about the Safe
Harbor program, and to view our certification, please visit http://www.export.gov/safeharbor/. This Privacy Policy
covers sites administered by us on behalf of customers and all information held by us and processed using systems
associated with our services.
This Privacy Policy and our privacy practices have been reviewed by eTrust, and have been awarded eTrust’s
“PrivacyTrust Seal.” In addition, our privacy practices and this Privacy Policy comply with eTrust’s program
requirements including transparency, accountability and choice regarding the collection and use of personal
information. eTrust's mission, as an independent third party, is to accelerate online trust among consumers and
organizations globally through its leading privacy Trustmark and innovative trust solutions.
Why We Collect/How We May Use Personally identifiable Information: We collect personally identifiable
information in order to, among other things, (a) set up and provide services to our customers, (b) process
customer payments, (c) improve our services, and (d) communicate with our customers. Customers may opt out of
providing information covered by this Privacy Policy by declining to be customers. Providing this information is
required to become a customer.
Sources of Personally identifiable Information: We receive and collect personally identifiable information from a
variety of sources as we interact with our customers and with the public. These sources include:
      E-mails, correspondence, and applications we receive from all sources.
      Cookies, URLs, web beacons, and other web identifiers we receive from visitors to our web sites.
      Credit card and credit information we receive as part of our billing and collection functions.
      Telephone calls, chat sessions, and blog postings we receive from all sources.
      Account information provided by our customers.
      Information posted on the Codero blog.
What Information We May Collect: Due to the nature of our business, we collect a wide variety of personally
identifiable information, including:
      Personal data such as individual names, addresses, telephone numbers, credit card numbers, and e-mail
          addresses.
      Business data such as business names, addresses, telephone numbers, credit card numbers, and e-mail
          addresses.
      Non-personally identifiable information for aggregation such as, among other things, visitor browser type
          and screen resolution.
                                                                      1
             Copyright © 2014 Codero. All rights reserved. 5750 W. 95th Street, Overland Park, KS 66207 – Last Updated 6/16/2014

Information We May Disclose To Third Parties: Codero does not sell or rent any personally identifiable
information we collect to third parties. However, we may disclose or transmit personally identifiable information
to third parties for specific purposes and situations, including:
      In response to a subpoena, court order, or other valid legal process.
      To process or collect customer payments.
      To enable third-party vendors to provide specific services to Codero, including, among others, retargeted
          ad placement services and website tracking, recording, testing, and optimization services.
      To prevent, investigate, or stop illegal or malicious activities including violations of our acceptable use
          policy, threats to our facilities, and threats to the physical safety of any person.
      To our affiliated companies or to any entity that acquires majority control of us or one of our business
          units through merger, acquisition, consolidation, or otherwise.
Note that any information submitted on the Codero blog is immediately viewable by the public.
Payment Information: We only collect payment from customers who have agreed to our terms of service. This
information is protected using industry standard methods. We do not collect financial information from non-
customers through or generally through our public website. When you provide us with payment information it is
collected on our payment page. Payment information you provide to us is stored on our servers and debited as set
out in our terms of service. When we are contacted by an individual who is authorized to make changes to your
account, we will remove, delete or add payment methods. When we collect payment information from you, it is
SSL encrypted from end-to-end. Credit card information that is stored by us is encrypted on our servers. Credit
card charges are executed through a merchant processing gateway, and all transactions are encrypted during
execution.
External Links: We have no control over the privacy policies of web sites whose links appear on our site(s). Please
review the privacy policies of those linked sites for an understanding of how they use information they collect from
you.
E-Mail Opt-Out: You may opt-out of receiving most e-mails from us by following the “unsubscribe” instructions
provided in the e-mails.
Cookies. Cookies are small data files that are placed automatically on a customer’s computer by our computers.
These data files are read by our computer to determine whether you have visited our site before, how often, the
length of time and which pages you view. We use cookies to keep customers logged into our service, to collect
transactional information about where our customers go during their use of our services and how they behave as
well as to set language preferences. Cookies are not used in conjunction with personally identifiable information,
and, other than as necessary to keep a customer logged into the services, do not identify an individual. Information
collected using cookies is not sold by us, or used outside the services, other than as necessary to provide the
services to customers.
Minors: The Codero website is not designed to be used by minors under 14 years old. It is not our intent to gather
personally identifiable information about anyone below the age of 14.
Appropriate Procedures: We have put in place reasonable measures and appropriate procedures for
implementing these policies and for safeguarding the information we collect from you. However, we cannot
guarantee that personally identifiable information we collect will never be disclosed in a manner inconsistent with
this Privacy Policy.
                                                                      2
             Copyright © 2014 Codero. All rights reserved. 5750 W. 95th Street, Overland Park, KS 66207 – Last Updated 6/16/2014

Questions: If you have any questions or concerns about this Privacy Policy, please contact us at
privacy@codero.com. If, however, you are unhappy with our response to your concerns, you can raise an issue
with eTrust, who are an independent third party dispute resolution service. They will work with us to ensure that
your query is resolved. You can contact eTrust here: http://www.etrust.org/about/privacy_contact.php.
If a customer wishes to access and/or update the information we have collected, the customer may either login to
our website or client systems and view and change its information. If a customer would like a list of systems
related to its account, this can also be obtained by logging into our customer portal at www.ServerPortal.com.
Deletion and Preservation of Information. Information covered by this Privacy Policy may be deleted upon a
customer’s request. We may keep information covered by this Privacy Policy for a period of six months from the
date of a customer’s termination of their relationship with us, or as required by law. Also, you may request that we
update or correct your personally identifiable information by contacting us at (877) 275-8763 (U.S.) or (858) 410-
6929 (Worldwide) or by writing us at:
Codero Hosting
5750 W. 95th St., Suite 300
Overland Park, KS 66207
Fax: (913) 890-7787
Updates: We may periodically update this Privacy Policy without notice to you. If we modify this Privacy Policy, we
will provide notice to customers through their ServerPortal.com account and display a banner in ServerPortal.com
for thirty days following a change. Please refer to this Privacy Policy regularly to remain updated about our current
privacy policies. Your continued use of our services after we post an updated Privacy Policy serves as your
acceptance of that updated policy.
                                                                      3
             Copyright © 2014 Codero. All rights reserved. 5750 W. 95th Street, Overland Park, KS 66207 – Last Updated 6/16/2014
